what I want to talk about is the way
that we've got we're kind of addicted to
a simplistic way of thinking about
intelligence right and actually many
people have an allergy to thinking about
it in a more complex way and you know
Howard Gardner and Curt Fisher I studied
with at Harvard all they wanted to do
was talk about it in a more complex way
and they had very little interest in
anything like general intelligence and
thought it was actually a concept that
was dangerous right Howard Gardner once
said to me know that intelligence is the
most political of all the psychological
concepts right because it becomes the
meritocracies kind of yardstick and so
yeah so that's a little bit of a
preamble to like okay let's liberate
thinking about intelligence from the
idea and start thinking of intelligence
in a more complex way to watch the full
episode or to subscribe to the podcast
click the link in the description or
visit us at neuro hacker.com slash
collective insights to celebrate the
launch of this podcast we're giving away
a bunch of great prizes including a six
month subscription of qualia for details
on how to enter the contest go to neuro
hacker com